bizdesign.com 2010-12-19

# BizSecure : Privacy Policy

In the course of serving its customers, BizSecure acquires, stores and transmits customer communications and information that customers may regard as private or sensitive. Some of this information - such as the customer's name, address, telephone number, and credit card data - is provided to BizSecure by its customers in order to establish service. Other information - such as the customer's account status, choice of services, and customer logs - is created and maintained by BizSecure in the normal course of providing service.

This Privacy Policy applies only to BizSecure's treatment of data collected online, and does not apply to any offline data collection practices or to the data collection practices of any third parties, BizSecure customers, or any entities affiliated with BizSecure. Also, please note that use of BizSecure's website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

BizSecure's policies and procedures for handling customer information have been created with the understanding that Internet technologies are still evolving and that Internet business methods are continuing to evolve to meet the needs and opportunities of the changing technologies. As a result, BizSecure's policies and procedures are subject to change. Changes will be posted to the website and users agree to be bound by those changes.

> Data Security   
> Email Links   
> Cookies   
> Log Files   
> Links   
> Third-Party Relationships   
> Opt Out & Modifications   
> Notification of Changes   
> Personal Information Disclosure

**Data Security**

BizSecure protects the confidentiality of its customers' information, account information and personal communications. To secure the information collected online, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure only appropriate use of information that is collected from customers, BizSecure has implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures, for information stored online and offline. Further, BizSecure requires that employees who have access keep customer information confidential.

When customers submit sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - (Secure Sockets Layer). While on a secure page, such as the BizSecure Hosting order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when customers are just 'surfing'.

BizSecure uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure once received. For example, BizSecure stores personal information provided by customers on computer systems with limited access, that are located in secured manned facilities. BizSecure's employees are trained and kept up-to-date on our security procedures. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [security@bizsecure.com](mailto:security@bizsecure.co).

BizSecure cautions its customers and website visitors that no medium of communication, including the Internet, is entirely secure. Accordingly, BizSecure cannot be responsible for loss, corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of personal information provided to our website, or for any damages resulting from such loss, corruption, unauthorized acquisition or unauthorized use.

**Email Links**

BizSecure uses email links on the customer feedback page to allow customers to contact us directly with any questions or comments that they may have.

BizSecure reads every message sent in and tries to reply promptly to every one. BizSecure uses the information customers provide us to respond directly to questions or comments. BizSecure may also retain customer comments to improve the site and program, or BizSecure may simply choose review and discard the information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are a mechanism to remember information about a visitor from one page to another. Web browsers store cookies so that the browser itself can remember some information and then, on request, pass all that information up to the server at one time. BizSecure use cookies to remember your name and the contents of your shopping cart. This allows customers to leave the BizSecure site, come back later, and still have the contents of their shopping cart intact. It also lets BizSecure personalize the customer experience, tailoring the content to each customer's interests. The BizSecure website requires the use of cookies. Turning off cookies or rejecting the batteries.com cookie will limit a customer's experience with our website.

Some of our BizSecure's business partners (e.g, ScanAlert and GeoTrust) use cookies on their websites. BizSecure has no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by BizSecure only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

**Log Files**

BizSecure uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track customer movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. BizSecure keeps this information for our internal use only and does not share it with third parties.

**Links**

The BizSecure web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we BizSecure is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

**Third-Party Relationships**

When you purchase from BizSecure, your credit card information, name, and billing address to credit card companies for verification, and to authorize your purchase. BizSecure supplies the customer's name and billing information to its partners (e.g, ScanAlert and GeoTrust) who use this information to deliver your purchase.

BizSecure do not sell, share, or rent your personal information with other third parties.

BizSecure may send offers to customers on behalf of third party partners. If a customer wishes to take advantage of the offer, the Customer will provide their information to BizSecure's partners directly. BizSecure will not share customer information with these third party partners. Please review the privacy policies of BizSecure's third party partners to determine how they will customer information.

In the case of a business transaction, including but not limited to, a merger or sale of a portion of BizSecure's assets, customer information will likely be part of the assets transferred. In this event, BizSecure will attempt to notify impacted customers that their information has been transferred.

**Opt Out & Modifications**

Customers may opt out of receiving notices of new or upgraded products from BizSecure and BizSecure partners by sending an email to [optout@bizsecure.com](mailto:optout@bizsecure.com). However, customers may not opt out of receiving information from BizSecure which is essential for maintaining or updating customers' accounts or system information.

Most customers may access and modify their personal information via their online personal control panel/account information page. All other customers may access and modify their personal information by contacting the appropriate BizSecure Billing organization.

Customers who need to correct or update their personal information (such as their email address), can do so by logging into their account or by emailing the customer support department at [support@bizsecure.com](mailto:support@bizsecure.com).

**Notification of Changes**

In the event of a change in policy, BizSecure will post a notice of the change on [www.bizsecure.com](http://www.bizsecure.com/), so customers are aware of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed. If at any point BizSecure decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, BizSecure will notify customers via email or by posting a prominent notice on [www.bizsecure.com](http://www.bizsecure.com/) 30 days prior to implementing the change. Customers will have a choice as to whether or not BizSecure will use their information in this manner.

**Personal Information Disclosure**

BizSecure will not otherwise disclose its customers' personal and account information unless BizSecure has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of BizSecure, BizSecure's customers, or others, or where BizSecure has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.

BizSecure also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that BizSecure stores or transmits for its customers. The circumstances under which BizSecure will disclose such electronic customer communications are when:

  1. it is necessary in order to provide service to the customer;  

  2. it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of BizSecure and its customers;  

  3. it is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that BizSecure determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and  

  4. it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by BizSecure and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.  

BizSecure disclaims any intention to censor, edit or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. BizSecure will, however, review, delete or block access to communications that may harm BizSecure, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which BizSecure may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of BizSecure's Acceptable Use Policy.

**Updated:** January 27, 2007
